Yes, that's why I'm here for the after talk.
nice to meet you.
Yangyang, nice to meet you.
Following on from the main story, please welcome Mr. Kasamino from Ebisu Junior High School.
please give my best regards.
And Naoto Sasaki from Eiichi Takebayashi, please give my best regards.
nice to meet you.
So, what shall we talk about?
When I saw your blog...
Recently
I saw on your blog that you've recently seen the highly acclaimed Detective Conan's "Submarine of Black Gold".
Yes.
And you like Conan a lot, don't you?
Did you go see the movie with your sister?
Yes, we were going to go a while ago.
Yes.
I wanted to talk to her about Conan, and I felt a little sad to go alone, so I made plans with my sister and we went.
I was a little sad to go alone, so I somehow managed to make plans with my sister.
I have a nickname "Nomaru", so I thought I'd give you one too.
Anemaru 1, Anemaru 2, Animal, and so on.
Do you call your sister by a formula?
I have two older sisters, so I was wondering what to call them, and ended up with 1 and 2.
So it's like "Masked Lighty" or "No. 1 and No. 2"?
Yes, I see.
I see.
But since we went to see the show together...
What do you think about Conan, Mr. Sasaki?
I've been watching the Conan series for a long time, but I haven't seen most of the episodes. But I saw the first episode, and after that, I kind of drifted away from it.
But Kazami-san said he saw the movie, so I thought I'd give it a watch.
It's highly rated, actually, and there are a lot of characters in it.
I think of Mouri Ran, the heroine or girlfriend, and that little girl Haibara Ai, who's gone small.
There are many attractive characters, but who is your favorite?
It's hard for me to choose.
Conan's cool, Shinichi Kudo's cool, Mr. Akai's cool.
I'm the type of person who sees a movie and thinks everything is cool and cute.
But this movie is about a girl named Hii Baraui.
Like Conan, she's a girl who took a drug that made her small, and she's the main character.
I think she's kind of my favorite girl in this movie.
She's my favorite girl in this movie.
Ai Hiwara is at the top of the list.
That character is very attractive.
But the main plot is more important.
I'm a little worried about sperm when I see the trailer.
That's right.
It's like, "Don't worry about it.
Like, "Ai, are you okay?
It's been a while since I watched a movie for the first time.
I can sort of understand the atmosphere of Conan.
I think it's because there is an element of mystery and suspense in the movie.
But even so, Conan's physical abilities and so on...
That's right.
I don't know how to say it.
I mean, he uses gadgets like skateboards.
I mean, it's fine for a kid to go skateboarding, but...
It's like the old Cagliostro movie, Lupin Yamase...
ignoring gravity, Kaede, the movie is bringing us right back.
Kaede: The movie is bringing him along quickly, and the physical abilities of the main characters are getting better and better, They're getting better and better!
Kaede It's like they're ready to compete in the Olympics. No, the Olympics are the same thing, but I think I'm going to participate in the Superhuman Olympics.
Kaede Yes, you're right, it's more than the Olympics.
And Molly Lan, the heroine, is a little bit like a sub this time.
Yes, but she's in charge of action.
What? He won the Kanto tournament, so he's a strong character.
Kusunoki is also a movie lover, and he's getting stronger and stronger...
Kusuda No, do you mean he's strong? I mean...
What? You did that? I mean...
Did you know? I mean...
It's amazing, but it's an animated film.
It's beyond human knowledge.
It's exciting because it's an animation beyond my ability.
It's exciting because it's an animation that transcends our abilities.
And there's also the Black Organization, which is mentioned in the previews and in the storyline.
The way they are depicted in the story is also very attractive, and the dark side of them is also shown.
It's not just enemies.
The relationships are complicated, so much so that sometimes you wonder who this person is.
Surprisingly, I don't know much about Conan, but even so, the characters are clearly portrayed, so I can understand their charms and what's going on.
You can understand what's going on, and you're not left behind.
Do Conan movies have violent scenes like that every year?
Yes. The first scene is the one where the criminal is chasing after him or holding a gun to his head.
The first scene is usually a criminal chasing and running away or holding a gun to his head.It starts with a scene of a man holding a gun to someone's head.
I was so violent that I thought for a moment that I was watching the wrong anime.
Do you often watch detective stories? Suspense?
I do...
I do, but...
Yes, I do.
Suspense and detective stories...
Especially in two-hour dramas nowadays.
There are scenes that have a standard plot.
The point is to go to the precipice at the end.
Like, at the end, they go to the precipice and hunt them down.
Katahira and Nagisa cornering him...
But there's also the usual Conan stuff like that.
I feel like there's a lot of chili in this Conan story.
Yes, there's this Dr. Akasa of Conan's who uses what he's made to defeat people.
Dr. Akasa in Conan's movies and animations.
I think there are a lot of movies and animations that use this gadget or item.
In this case, he tells us that he's going to use this gadget or item.
In the movie, Dr. Akasa is so cute!
In the movie, Dr. Akasa has a very smug look on his face.
In the movie, Dr. Akasa was very smug and said, "I made this.
So that's part of it, too.
There's a lot of foreshadowing, so I think it's really fun to watch the movie while thinking about how it's going to turn out.
I understand. Of course, after watching a movie, you do think about it, don't you?
I think about what I should have done differently in each scene, but surprisingly, in Conan movies, you can change your mind from the beginning to the end in a good way.
It's like you can change your mind in a good way.
I thought that was part of the charm of the movie.
Yes, I think so.
I'm very happy to be able to talk about this.
And I'm a guesser, so I'm trying not to spoil the story.
I'm taking a bit of a detour here.
There's a risk I'll tell you everything, so please don't say that.
I'll do that, but since when do you like Conan?
I've been watching Conan for a long time.
I was in the fourth grade of elementary school when I saw my first Conan movie, and I've been hooked ever since.
We all get excited talking about how the anime is connected to the next movie and how we're thinking about it and how the next movie will turn out.
Oh, and April's coming to an end, too... so everyone's talking about it.
It's a movie that's made every year.
This season... not this one... the cherry blossoms... are in bloom... or are in leaf... but you can see them in this way...
I think it's a continuation of what you can see in the film.
I don't want to recommend it to everyone, but for those who see it in Asia, or for those who haven't seen it, you should do so because there are a lot of connections with the anime.
I think it's better to see the movie from the side.
So it's better to watch it side by side?
Both the animation and the movie?
But there's an important story in the anime first, so please look it up.
This circle is related to this circle.
I think you will probably find that this circle is related to this circle.
So, let's look at the rings that interest you.
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
I see.
There are a lot of them, aren't there?
A lot of manga and anime.
So, let's say you've seen this movie, and you want to keep it.
If you want to go back to the series, or the ones that are done every week, you can go back a little bit and see what's there.
So you can go back a little bit to the series, or the weekly series, and see what else is related to it?
Yes, if you look up the episodes in which Ai-chan appears as the main character, you will find that this circle appears as the main character in many of the anime series.
I'm sure it's there.
If you look at the times when Ai-chan is in the center of the movie, you will probably discover that this is the case in the movie as well.
I think so.
So you've seen the film once, you've stood around and watched it six times, can you watch it again?
I think that if you see it a second time, you can understand the foreshadowing of the connection.
I think you'll enjoy it. How many times have you seen it? How many times have you seen it? That's fast, isn't it? I've seen it twice in this short period of time.
I saw it about three days later. I'm watching it soon.
I'm that crazy about Conan, but I'm glad to see Nonakamaru talking so fast.
I'm glad to hear that you're talking too fast and that Mr. Sasaki didn't take notes this time.
I hope you'll watch from the first episode, and I hope you'll watch from the most important episode, because there are a lot of movies, and yes, this is for Conan's swamp, too.
Yes, I think it would be good to hear about it.
Yes, Yes, that's what I meant.
Thank you very much for the after talk, which was very exciting.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.